topgolf.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Topgolf

**_UPDATED: August 2, 2018_**

Topgolf International, Inc., a company having its principal place of business at 8750 N. Central Expressway, Suite 1200, Dallas, TX 75231, and its subsidiaries ("Topgolf" or "we" or "our" or "us") are committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personally identifiable information collected about you ("personal information"), what we do with it and with whom we share it. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal information at our physical locations ("Locations") or through this website at <https://www.topgolf.com/> and mobile application ("Site").

Please note that the headings contained in this Privacy Policy are inserted for convenience of reference only and shall not in any way define or affect the meaning, construction or scope of any of the provisions contained in this Privacy Policy.

PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AGREEMENT FOR THE SITE CAREFULLY. AS PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOUR USE OF THE SITE SIGNIFIES YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS AND CONDITIONS AGREEMENT. 

###   
Summary of Key Points

**Information We Collect** | 

We collect your name and contact information, and other information you provide us through registration pages, surveys and other submissions through this Site and at the Locations.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
---|---  
  
**How Personal Information We Collect is Used**

| 

We use your information to respond to your requests for information and otherwise provide you with products and services, display in-game statistics at Locations, and analyze customer behaviors and trends to enhance your experiences.  
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Site Usage Information & Cookies**

| 

We use cookies and similar technologies to help provide our Site, offer you a more personalized user experience, and market products and services to you.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Mobile Terms & Conditions**

| 

With your consent, we will send certain marketing text messages. However, you can unsubscribe from such messages at any time.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Contests and Sweepstakes**

| 

You are required to share certain personal information to enter contests and sweepstakes. Certain contests and sweepstakes are subject to their own terms and conditions.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Sharing Your Personal Information**

| 

We share your personal information about you with third parties to perform the purposes for which the information is collected, complete transactions on your behalf, respond to requests, and fulfill other business and compliance purposes.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Children's Privacy**

| 

We do not target or knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Security of Your Personal Information**

| 

We maintain and require appropriate technical, administrative and physical security measures designed to protect your personal information.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

| 

Changes to the Privacy Policy will be reflected at the top of this Privacy Policy, and we will obtain your consent as required by applicable law.   
Click here to learn more.  
  
**Data Subject Rights** ****

| 

You have certain rights to request access, rectification, deletion or other actions regarding your personal information where required by applicable law.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Links to Other Sites**

| 

This Site includes links and references to other websites administered by unaffiliated third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such third party websites.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Cross-Border Data Transfers**

| 

We provide appropriate protections for cross-border transfers of your personal information where specified by law.   
Click here to learn more.   
  
**Other issues** ****

| 

We provide other information in this Privacy Policy about: (i) the legal basis for our collection and processing of personal information; (ii) the consequences for not providing personal information; (iii) automated decision-making; (iv) do-not-track ("DNT") signals; (v) data retention; and (vi) links to third party websites.   
Click here to learn more.  
  
**Questions and More Information**

| 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.   
Click here to learn more.  
  
####   
Information We Collect 

Personal information collected about you includes your name and address, telephone number and email address, and other information we maintain about you when you visit our Locations and voluntarily contact us through this Site, including information you provide on sign-up and membership registration pages, surveys, or other submission and/or purchases through this Site. We also collect certain personal information through your use of a mobile device, such as smartphones, tablets and iPads. This information includes your mobile device identifier, device type and IP address.  To learn more about how to control the collection of the information we collected about you from such devices, please see the **Site Usage Information & Cookies **section below.

####   
How Personal Information We Collect is Used

The personal information collected is combined with other information collected about you and is used and disclosed in a number of ways by us, to help us better understand and serve our customers, including:

  * providing you with, or otherwise responding to your requests for, information and/or services, including but not limited to e-newsletters, marketing programs, forward-to-a-friend or other options in our marketing programs;
  * providing you with information about new products or services, events at our Locations, events that Topgolf sponsors, including contests, sweepstakes and surveys, and other special offers and marketing programs, which may include information about partner companies or other programs any of us or them are involved with;
  * displaying a member’s first and last name on Leaderboards at a Topgolf Location as well as on any digital platform such as this Site;
  * enhancing our customers' experiences at our Locations and on this Site;
  * analyzing customer behaviors and trends;
  * conducting research and analysis and to otherwise measure the effectiveness of our online and offline marketing efforts and to develop products, services and marketing programs;
  * coordinating program activities and communications with other marketing programs conducted by us.

We do not sell or rent to third parties any of the personal information that you provide to us through this Site or at our Locations, or authorize any of our suppliers to sell or rent any such personal information, and we do not authorize any of our suppliers to make independent use of your personal information for their own purposes, including but not limited to direct marketing.  However, aggregated information about customers utilizing this Site, our social media pages (e.g., Likes, impressions, views), in surveys or otherwise providing information to Topgolf will be utilized by Topgolf and/or suppliers in connection with research, benchmarking and other like uses related to general usage analytics. 

####   
Site Usage Information & Cookies 

Like most websites, this Site tracks the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, pages visited per use, browser type, IP addresses, exit page, duration of use, and operating system type, in order to administer the Site and analyze trends and statistics to evaluate our visitors' preferences and the effectiveness of the Site. We share anonymous, aggregated statistics about visitors to this Site with third parties, and we allow third parties to collect aggregate data through this Site and/or supplier sites accessible from or though this Site for these purposes.

For purposes of collecting the aggregate data mentioned above and for other reasons stated here, this Site uses cookies and related technologies ("cookies") to enhance the browsing and usage experience on our Site. "Cookies" are small files or records that are placed on a visitor's device or browser (by us or a third party provider of ours) to collect information about your activities on our Site. The information captured about your activities on our Site will make it possible for us: (i) to speed navigation and provide you with custom-tailored content; (ii) to remember information you gave to us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site; (iii) to monitor the effectiveness of certain of our marketing email campaigns; (iv) to monitor the total number of visitors, pages viewed, and banners served on our Site; and (v) to enforce limitations on downloads described for online coupons and other similar offers. If you refuse cookies, your experience on our Site may be affected — for example, you may not be able to utilize all of the functions on this Site. As detailed below, we also allow certain trusted partners to place cookies on our Site and services in order to provide personalized marketing to you. 

**Advertising  
**We use third-party advertising companies to place cookies on our Site and services in order serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this Site and our services and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Specifically, advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria-for example, people aged 30-50 from a particular geographic area. We do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement. 

**Your Choices**  
You can review your Internet browser settings, typically under the sections "Help" or "Internet Options" and use our [cookie management page](https://topgolf.com/us/company/cookies/) to exercise choices you have for certain cookies, including for interest-based advertising. If you disable or delete certain non-essential cookies, you might not be able to access or use important functions or features of this Site or services, and you may be required to re-enter your log-in details.  Please note you may also still receive advertisements from the relevant ad serving company you opted out of, but the ads will not be tailored to your interests. For our mobile app, please review your device settings or third party tools available. 

####   
Mobile Terms & Conditions 

  * You must be 13 years of age or older to participate in the Topgolf mobile text program.
  * By providing your mobile phone at opt-in, you consent to receive future recurring automated marketing text messages to the mobile number provided from or on behalf of Topgolf. You also acknowledge that your agreement to receive these messages isn’t required as a condition of purchase.
  * **Message & data rates may apply.** All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. Topgolf does not charge you for sending or receiving text messages to **68633**.
  * You can unsubscribe at any time by texting **"STOP"** to **68633**. A text will be sent confirming your removal. Topgolf reserves the right to remove subscribers from our messaging database. For more info, text **"HELP"** to **68633** or [contact us online](http://vibes.com/help).
  * This program is not available on all carriers, and Topgolf is not liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages or undelivered messages.
  * Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service includes your cell phone number, your carrier's name, the date, time and content of your messages, and other information you provide to Topgolf as part of this service. We use this information to contact you with products or services that may be of interests to you and to provide the services you request from us. Your information will not be shared with any third parties for their own purposes. View our [Privacy Policy](https://topgolf.com/us/company/privacy-policy/)

####   
Contests/Sweepstakes

On occasion, Topgolf may conduct or sponsor contests/sweepstakes with the opportunity to win prizes. Each contest/sweepstakes has its own terms and conditions ("Official Contest/Sweepstakes Rules"). As part of entering a contest or sweepstakes online through this Site or through a third party provider site, certain personal information (including your name, address, phone number) is required. This information will be used as described in the applicable Official Contest/Sweepstakes Rules. 

####   
Sharing Your Personal Information 

We share your personal information with service providers, such as email marketing service providers, for purposes of providing the Site and services to you, who we require to provide reasonable security for personal information and to only use your personal information on our behalf. 

The law requires that we, and our suppliers may be required to, share your personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or other like orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we and our suppliers reserve the right to use and disclose your personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, and/or violations of this Site's Terms and Conditions statement as required by law. 

In the event of a transfer or sale of some or all of our business or assets, we will disclose your personal information to those involved in such a transfer or sale of business or assets. 

####   
Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) years. This Site is directed to persons who are at least thirteen (13) years of age. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information through any point of contact, we ask to be contacted at the below address or email address, and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files. If Topgolf has actual knowledge that personal information about a person under the age of 13 has been collected without appropriate parental consent, then Topgolf will take the appropriate steps to delete such information.

####   
Security of Your Personal Information 

Topgolf takes and requires that its suppliers take appropriate steps to keep your personal information confidential. Although we can't guarantee that there will never be a security problem, we have in place appropriate security measures to guard against the loss or misuse of the information collected on this Site and at our Locations.

####   
Changes in Our Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy from time to time — for example, by altering our policy on sharing personal information. Be sure to check this page periodically for updates, and we will ask for your consent to the updates if required by applicable law. 

####   
Changing Your Information - Data Subject Rights 

Moved? Changed e-mail addresses? If you need to update or verify your personal information, please contact us as detailed below. Upon request, Topgolf will remove your personal information from our active database as soon as reasonably possible, unless we need to retain information for dispute resolution, troubleshooting and other valid legal or business reasons. 

Where required by applicable law, you also have the right to: obtain confirmation of the existence of certain personal information relating to you, to verify its content, origin, and accuracy, as well as the right to access, review, obtain a copy, port, delete, or to block or withdraw consent to the processing of certain personal information (without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal), by contacting us as detailed below. **Additionally, you have the right to object to our use of personal information for direct marketing.** Please note that we need to retain certain personal information as required or permitted by applicable law.

Contact us at email [update@topgolf.com](mailto:update@topgolf.com) or in writing at Topgolf International, Inc., 8750 N. Central Expressway (Suite 1200), Dallas, TX 75231, ATTN: Marketing Resources to request access to or exercise rights to your personal information. 

####   
Links to Other Sites 

This Site provides links to websites not operated by Topgolf, including our suppliers or partners. Topgolf requires that its suppliers take steps to keep your personal information confidential. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Topgolf assumes no responsibility for third party websites, including but not limited to the privacy practices of these third party sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave this Site, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of every website that collects personal information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and our Locations.

Although we endeavor to alert you when you are about to leave our Site when you click on a link to a third party site, Topgolf does not guarantee that you will receive this alert when you leave this Site. It is your responsibility to determine when you have left this Site. 

####   
Cross-Border Data Transfers

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal information will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. Where permitted by applicable law, by submitting your personal information to this Site and Locations, you consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States. We take steps to securely maintain personal information transferred to the United States. 

####   
Other Issues

 _ **What is the legal basis of processing?**  
_Some jurisdictions require an explanation of the legal basis for the collection and processing of personal information. We have several different legal grounds on which we collect and process personal information, including: (a) as necessary to perform a transaction (such as when we respond to your requests); (b) as necessary to comply with a legal obligation (such as when we use personal information for recordkeeping to substantiate tax liability); (c) consent (where you have provided consent as appropriate under applicable law, such as for marketing or certain cookies); and (d) necessary for legitimate interests (such as when we act to maintain our business generally).  With respect to legitimate interests, except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of you which require protection of personal information, such legitimate interests are the fulfilment of the processing purposes described in this Privacy Policy that are not necessary for the performance of a contract or for our compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject.

 _ **What are the consequences of not providing personal information?**  
_You are not required to provide all personal information identified in this Privacy Policy to use the Site or services, but certain functionality will not be available if you do not provide personal information.  If you do not provide personal information, we may not be able to enter you into contests, respond to your requests, or provide you with marketing that we believe you would find valuable.

 _ **Do we engage in automated decision-making without human intervention?**  
_We do not use automated decision-making without human intervention, including profiling, in a way that produces legal effects concerning you or otherwise significantly affects you. 

_**Does the Site honor do-not-track ("DNT") signals sent via browsers?**  
_Given the divergent practices of organizations that offer browsers and the lack of a standard in the marketplace, we generally do not respond to DNT signals at this time.

 _ **How long do we retain personal information?**  
_We typically retain personal information related to marketing activities for as long as you accept marketing communications from us, and we will securely delete such data in accordance with applicable law upon request.  For personal information that we collect and process for other purposes, we typically retain such personal information for no longer than the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, and as otherwise needed to address tax, corporate, compliance, litigation, and other legal rights and obligations.

####   
Questions and More Information 

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us by sending an email to [privacy@topgolf.com](mailto:privacy@topgolf.com). 

If you reside in the European Economic Area, you can also write to us at the following address:

Attn: Privacy  
Topgolf Sweden AB  
Svärdvägen 11 4tr, SE-182 33 Danderyd  
Sweden

Please note that you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

This Privacy Policy was last updated: August 2, 2018

This Privacy Policy is effective as of: May 25, 2018
